The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives a magicless boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the next wizard king.
Though Asta's situation is practically unheard of,
there are others residing in this kingdom
who possess at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely use spells at all.
They make up a very small minority,
living their lives in the shadows.
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
Where am I?
What am I doing here?
Wait, I remember!
You're finally awake.
It's you.
You're friends with Asta and my brother.
Yes.
Our magic's been sealed, so we can't escape.
And I borrowed a tracking device from Asta,
but they took that too.
Who kidnapped us?
Do you know these people?
Mm-mm.
The only thing this girl and I have in common
is that we were accused of working with the devil.
They're probably planning to use us for leverage somehow.
This is all for the sake of justice.
Yes indeed, Master Cobwe.
It's our responsibility to rid this kingdom of the devil's evil servants
and to rebuild what they destroyed.
It shall be done at all costs.
So,
何度も 何度も 何度も 目の前の今を超えるさ
何度も 何度も 何度も 涙を希望に変えていこう
七色の 日常を進め 永遠に光れ
シャインラインカテモン
天使と 悪魔が 交際してく
世界は 宇宙だらけさ
思い通りじゃない
そのくらいで 明ける夢はダサい
そう 何度も 何度も 何度も 夢の前の
壁を超えるさ
何度も 何度も 良さを未来に繋げよう
七色の 日常を進め 永遠に光れ
You shine like a diamond
There are so many people...
Our kingdom deserves justice and the devil banishers are going to make sure we get it!
Kill those traitors now!
Just get on with it!
We wanna see blood!
I can't wait for the show!
Asserts them right!
This is insane!
They'll all die for disrespecting my angel!
They sure are amped up about watching a couple of girls die!
This is so terrifying!
Yeah!
Hang in there you two!
The black bulls are coming to the rescue!
Listen up everyone!
We got a message from Julius on the way!
It looks like all squads are in position!
The execution's scheduled for noon so we've only got a little while left to wait!
We don't know their numbers but I'm sure they'll be using a combination of spells and various drugs!
Though this mission may prove difficult, I'll trust you'll do everything you can to recover the captives!
The Silver Eagles and the Crimson Lion Kings will assist with the rescue and make sure that none of the civilians in the crowd are harmed in the process!
The Blue Rose Knights and Green Praying Mantises will patrol the square at all times!
And given their closeness to the situation, the Black Bulls will be the main squad in charge of saving the hostages!
Sounds good!
One thing though, there's a certain someone over here who's got nothing to do with the mission whatsoever!
I'm guessing he tagged along out of guilt seeing as how his subordinates are probably behind this whole mess!
But I think it's gonna be bad news if he decides to act on his own!
This rescue is top priority!
Can we trust you'll go along with our operation, Dom Natio?
Yes, that is my intention, sir, but I need to confirm something first!
If Asta uses the Devil's power in front of this large crowd, then it will only create more anger and confusion!
So I'm asking...
Of course he's not gonna do it!
Did you think we'd be that stupid?
Alright squad, everyone but Ghosh and the Kid keep an eye on the square like we discussed!
These girls are two of our own, so don't screw up!
Right!
Good luck!
Be safe!
The other squads are watching over the Noble Realm, as you requested!
Right!
We have to keep in mind that the execution could be a ruse to distract us while they cause trouble elsewhere!
We'd better make sure we put a stop to their plans!
If they carry this out, it'll throw the Kingdom into an even greater panic!
Yes, it's up to the Magic Knights!
We haven't seen anything unusual yet!
I hope the rescue mission goes smoothly!
With Captain Vongence away protecting the border, we can't contribute much to the main part of the plan, but let's be on alert!
Right!
Why do we have to patrol?
You're the best fighter, you should be right in the middle of the action!
The plan's been made, that's that!
Hey, wait for me, you know!
It's almost time!
The purveyors of justice will soon arrive!
Forget the Magic Knights and the Magic Parliament!
Only the Devil Banishers can set this Kingdom right!
I agree!
Someone must uphold the law!
I bet those guys are in the crowd somewhere!
How are we going to find them?
Man, these people have lost it!
Makes me wonder if they've all been drugged too!
I can't stand this!
Look, Captain, you've gotta let me go down there!
Oh, can I come with you?
Right down!
If you go waltzing in there, you'll blow the lid off this whole plan!
Okay, but we can't just do nothing!
You're the ace in the hole, kid!
We need to wait for our moment!
Right.
We still haven't seen any sign of them yet.
Odd.
It's noon now.
Where are they?
I gotta say, I'm not really seeing anyone who looks suspicious.
Stay on guard.
Will do, shark.
Okay!
They're not even here on time!
Hey, witch!
If you want your friends to survive, then you'll do as we say.
You make one wrong move, and we'll kill the hostages before they even get out in front of the crowd.
Start walking slowly toward the exit.
I knew I wouldn't sense their mana, but I didn't expect them to approach me like this.
It's all right.
I'm sure the others can pull it off without me.
Understood.
And there they are.
Greetings, enemies of the Devil!
The time has come to strike in the name of righteousness!
We are the Devil Banishers!
Those who wish for the Devil's demise!
Settledale.
Now I can understand how they were able to conceal their mana so completely.
Except that it looks like only those three are wearing them.
The evidence of this woman's guilt is obvious!
Notice the pair of horns on her head!
Proof that she worked with the Devil and used forbidden magic!
How disgusting!
That girl's evil incarnate!
The child Dexter, whose brother is a former criminal, is also the Devil's servant!
We have undeniable proof that their actions have destroyed countless lives!
How could anyone condemn that sweet little face?
Kill them both now!
They should have been put to death a long time ago!
Lord Damnatio, if that barrier spell explodes, it's going to harm a large number of civilians.
Kabwe, I understand that you seek justice, but how can you expect the innocent to pay the price for it?
That magic, since it's a barrier, I'm guessing one of Scaleboy's lackeys is responsible.
But we mustn't forget!
There's one boy who was possessed by the Devil himself, and we hate him most of all!
That traitor's name...
Is Asta!
Every drop of blood spilled by the eye of the midnight sun is on his hands!
We know that you're here with us, Asta!
And we want nothing more than to see you dead!
It's just like Captain Yami said...
Even if Asta took the blame for that, they still wouldn't stop this!
However, if you come forward immediately and plead guilty, we will allow your two companions to walk free!
Hero... free!
Why haven't you responded?
It must mean that you value your own life over those of your cohorts!
Of course he does!
That's what a Devil would do!
Asta would never abandon his friends!
Very well. We have our answer.
I'm over here!
Good. Now approach the stage.
I don't see Vanessa, but there's no time to track her down now.
You little freak!
That's him, everyone! He's the villain who destroyed our kingdom!
You murdered my entire family!
Kill him!
Serves him right!
Look, I swear! We don't work with the Devil!
Shut your mouth, demon!
Stop right there.
We'll be confiscating your grimoire as well.
What, did that ruin your plans?
We know that you intended to use anti-magic to cancel out the barrier we've set up around the square.
Come on! Execute him already!
If I take the blame, then you'll let them go?
Well, yes, that is what I just said.
Then step away from them!
And put down your swords!
Certainly.
Now then, hand over your grimoire.
Okay.
Hmm?
No!
What?
Too off the...
All we needed was for you to look away from the hostages for a couple of seconds.
Dark magic.
Dark clothes.
Lightless.
Run!
They're so much so much pain in me!
Ahhhhh!
Your sleeping potions won't work this time!
Paper magic.
Dagger folding.
Early summer rain!
Hurry!
Now's your chance!
Nice cry.
You ready? Let's go.
Okay, now it's getting interesting.
Run!
The others are buying some time.
Transparency magic. Share the same fate.
Mero! Marie! Come back!
Move it! Get away!
Hey, kid, where are you?
A truck? Water magic!
Sea dragon's lair!
Something's wrong. I can't control it.
Do something! It's gonna close and it's glitched me!
What happened? And why don't you have Marie?
Asta went after her.
I'm sorry, I was gonna go too, but the smoke's affecting my eyesight and I can't really use my magic.
The traps that I set up around the square aren't responding.
Not sure what, but there's something in that smoke that messes with mana.
If that's how they want to play, fine.
That's what I'm talking about, Captain Yami. Way to teach him a lesson, huh?
Now, help all the civilians evacuate.
Fall to your knees.
Thank you for tons of force of fate, so all we were trying to do was to get you away from the square.
I see. Except, even without altering fate.
I already know that my friends have set the two hostages free.
Which means I don't have to cooperate with you.
We know we can't beat a magic knight.
We also know you read the memories of those you capture.
In other words, our job is done.
We went into this operation completely prepared to sacrifice ourselves.
They just took their own lives like it was nothing.
I don't know what their plan is, but how could it have been that important to them?
I feel their key. They must be close.
It's all over.
Chasing us down without thinking is exactly what we wanted you to do.
Huh, fool. Time to surrender the grimoire.
And don't resist, or we'll exterminate your friends.
Master!
Don't worry! We'll get out of this!
I'd like to see you try that without using the Devil's power.
Shall we take them away before the others arrive, Master Cobwe?
No, I'd rather take care of them right here.
That's not what we planned.
The Magic Knights are powerful. I underestimated their strength.
We were lucky to get this far.
If we want to succeed, then our safest bet is to kill them now, while we have the chance.
But, sir...
You coward! Why are you so scared?
Don't disrespect him!
You little...
No!
You won't be able to avoid these.
If you do, they'll just hit the girl!
Paper magic! Dagger folding early summer rain!
What's happening?
This must be them. The Devil Banishers.
You know? Where'd you come from?
Oh, we were just in the neighborhood, so we figured we would drop by. That's no biggie.
We were only supposed to be patrolling.
But I believe Captain Vongence would probably want us to intervene.
Asta! I hope you're not injured!
I'm fine! Just help Nero!
You'll pay for this!
If they hadn't shown up, we would have had Asta for sure!
We need to retreat before they catch us!
Give Nero back!
That's not going to happen! Now stand down, or we'll slit her throat!
Really? They're running away?
Unbelievable.
They say that a Devil dwells in the Five-Leaf Grimoire.
So we'll be taking it off your hands.
No, wait!
Asta!
They're gone!
Make sure Marie's okay, Mimosa.
Sure!
So they took your grimoire.
They really thought of everything.
Not everything. Asta's magic doesn't come from his grimoire.
What do you mean?
I don't follow.
That's right.
Asta!
They really thought of everything.
Not everything. Asta's magic doesn't come from his grimoire.
Asta!
That's right.
I'll get an arrow back. And my grimoire. Because my magic is never giving up!
Marie!
Please don't die!
I need my angel with me forever!
Don't leave me behind!
I can't bear it!
She's just sleeping.
Owen says she needs rest, but she'll wake up later on.
So, she's gonna be okay?
Yes.
Good.
I guess this means that I owe you again.
Today we discovered that my subordinates were indeed responsible for the kidnappings.
Please allow me to apologize for my oversight.
You said they had a strong sense of justice.
But taking a whole crowd prisoner doesn't exactly scream do-gooders to me.
I wonder if the Devil Banishers are being manipulated by a completely different entity.
You're right, they did take Asta's grimoire.
Someone other than Cobway could have wanted it for their own purposes.
Hey, wait.
You're throwing ideas out there and you weren't even at the first meeting.
After you cried like a baby and made a big thing out of proving your loyalty, too.
To clarify,
I was the one who asked him to go keep an eye on the borders.
If the Spade Kingdom were to make a move right now,
there'd be chaos.
Everyone, there's something that I need to show you.
We investigated the memories of the Devil Banishers we took into custody.
Apparently, their organization is largely made up of paid hires.
I apologize for the interruption.
What's wrong?
We just received a message from Cobway.
Cobway?
We're listening.
Where are you?
It's a lie.
These people aren't trying to bring about the Devil's demise.
Not at all.
The truth is that
they're after the Devil's power.
What do you mean?
This organization actually worships the Devil.
They're called
Devil Believers.
The Devil's
Haleiに
転んで
傷ついて
気づけば
誰ももう
どこにもいない
歪んだ世界に魔法の言葉で 光が射すなら飛びつくんだろう
今目の前に残るのは希望か
掴みかけたわずかな幸福が まだ消せない誓い叫んでる 忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くだって 全然届かなくても 信じる君は足掻いて前を向いている
だから枯れないように柄がって 描いた夢また歩き出せるきっと
僕を呼ぶ声だ
話します
読壇
będziemy